Guide to the Elliott School of International Affairs records, 1907-2005 RG0015
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- School files, 1964-1993; RG0015 Series 4; 10.5 Linear feet
  - Work Study Program - State Dept. Information; Student letters; Response, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    formerly folder 168
  - Work Study-Service Learning Intern Program, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    formerly folder 169
  - School files, undated (Box 7)
  - Dean's Appointment Books, 1986-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 170
  - Program Marketing Materials, undated; 1 (Box SHARED 2, Folder 8)